videoconvertertool.net 2013-12-10

# Site Privacy Policy

**VIDEOCONVERTERTOOL Privacy Policy**

[Last updated July, 2013]

When you use this Website [VIDEOCONVERTERTOOL.NET](http://videoconvertertool.net/) website ("Website", "Us" or "We") and the VIDEOCONVERTERTOOL software ("Software"), you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected and stored by Us when you make use of the Website or Software downloaded from the Website, and how the information will be used.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time we ask you to check back the most updated form of Privacy Policy as indicated below. 

YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SOFTWARE AND/OR THIS WEBSITE AFTER THIS PRIVACY POLICY HAS BEEN AMENDED SHALL BE DEEMED AS YOUR CONTINUED ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS AMENDED.

PLEASE NOTE: WE WILL NOT USE OR SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH ANYONE EXCEPT AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**1\. Information Collected**

1.1.Personal Information:

We may collect some personal information that you explicitly provide (for example, in the process of registration to the Website services) and which identifies your personally, such as your name, email address, services purchased, etc. ("Personal Information").

1.2.Non-Personal Information:

We collect some non-identifying information regarding your use of our Website and Software, including but not limited to, type of device on which Software is used and installed, applications with which the Software has interacted, advertisements viewed, pages browsed, search inquiries, the type of browser you are using, your IP address, the URL you have come from and the time spent at that URL, cookies and your domain type and server ("Non-Personal Information").

**2\. Children Policy**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13). In the event that we learn that Personal Information was collected from a child under age of thirteen (13) without verification of parental consent, we will take adequate measures to delete that information as quickly as possible.

**3\. Software and Website Updates**

The Software may perform regular checks for software updates on our servers and may download such updates when needed.

**4\. Use of Collected Information**

4.1.Personal Information:

Personal Information shall be used solely in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

4.2.We will not disclose your Personal Information to any third party, unless: (i) required to do so as part of any legal proceedings conducted between you and the Website; (ii) Required to do so by court order; (iii) In case the activity of the Website is transferred to a third party, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms

4.3.Non-Personal Information:

Non-Personal Information shall be used to ensure the adequate operation, improve, modify, cancel, enrich or adjust the Website and/or the Software.

4.4.We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information to third parties, including, advertisers, sponsors, business partners, investors, affiliates and consultants, at our sole discretion.

**5\. Cookies**

We use Cookies in order to ensure proper operation, collect Non-Personal Information, verify information, tailor the Website and Software to your specific preferences and ensure information security.

Please note that modern browsers enable you to disable Cookies, however, this may interfere with your use of the Website or its services.

**6\. Third Party Advertisements**

We may use third-party advertising partners in order to serve advertisements on our Website. Such parties may use Cookies placed on your computer in order to adjust the advertisements presented on the Website. Such use is subject to the privacy policy of those parties and is not subject to these terms, we recommend you to review said policies.

**7\. Information Security**

Note that although we take measures to secure the information and reduce the risk of unwanted disclosure, we cannot guarantee the information will not be exposed as a result of unauthorized penetration to our servers.

**8\. Support**

If you feel that your privacy was invaded and/or if you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us directly at [support@VIDEOCONVERTERTOOL.NET](mailto:support@VIDEOCONVERTERTOOL.NET), and our privacy officer shall investigate and post its report promptly.
